#### MAGNUS LYNGRA

Computer engineer at UiT - The Arctic University of Norway 41611628 • magnuslyngra@live.no • https://www.linkedin.com/in/magnuslyngra/ • Tromsø

## Summary

A software developer that loves to build things and working for continuous improvements. Do my best to contribute to a fun and engaging working environment. Enjoy technology and have experience with technologies like SQL/GraphQL and Python. A supporter of open source software and a diehard linux enthusiast.

## **Experience**

### UiT- The Arctic University of Norway

Tromsø, Norway

Head Engineer

06/2024 - Present

Working in a shared position between the education department and the IT department, trying to bring them closer together in relevant areas. This includes keeping a close dialogue between the two departments and furthering collaboration between them. I also assist in developing existing and new systems and solutions for the departments. This includes working with SQL, Python, GraphQL and other relevant technologies.

• Highlight your accomplishments, using numbers if possible.

UiT- The Arctic University of Norway

Norway

Head Engineer

03/2022 - 10/2024

Company Description

- Advanced audio/video support
- Recording and streaming of lectures, courses and conferences
- Operation and management of audio/video equipment

UiT- The Arctic University of Norway

Tromso, Norway

Adviser

06/2019 - 03/2022

Admissions department

• Highlight your accomplishments, using numbers if possible.

UiT- The Arctic University of Norway

Location

**Higher Executive Officer** 

02/2016 - 05/2019

Company Description

• Highlight your accomplishments, using numbers if possible.

NAV Location

Veileder 08/2015 - 02/2016

Company Description

- Veileder NAVs brukere om rettigheter om muligheter man har gjennom NAV på generelt grunnlag.
- Vi gir mennesker muligheter.

UiT The Arctic University of Norway

Location

Consultant

09/2014 - 08/2015

UiT The Arctic University of Norway

Tromso Area, Norway

Secretary

01/2014 - 08/2015

Narvesen

Location

Salesman

03/2012 - 09/2013

Studenthuset Driv

Tromsø, Norway

Volunteer

09/2011 - 06/2012

**Education** 

UiT- The Arctic University of Norway

Bachelor's degree, Computer Science

08/2021 - 06/2024

# Education

UiT- The Arctic University of Norway Master's Degree, Political Science and Government	01/2013 - 12/2015
UiT- The Arctic University of Norway Bachelor's degree, Political Science and Government	01/2010 - 12/2013